Kehinde OLUMOFE. Msc Industrial Sociology

Nationality: Nigerian. State of origin: Ondo state Date of Birth: 05/04/1989

Home Address: 3, along lane Street, Beside IITA barb wire, off Akingbile-Moniya road,

Ibadan.

Contact Details: <u>victorolumofe@gmail.com</u>, +2347033153669, +2348027706358

Summary:

A Master Degree holder in Industrial Sociology and a highly motivated, self-directed TEAM MANAGER with several years of experience in team coordination and management roles with a consistent track record of achievement across all functions.

Work Experience:

August 2015 - July 2016

National Youth Service Corps

Akpabuyo LG council- Cross River

Position: Office Assistant

• In-charge of the servicom department

Independent National Electoral Commission

Position: Presiding officer

• Organizing, supervising, collating and announcing election results.

September 2016 - February 2017

Initiative for Community & Empowerment

Program officer

 Management of day to day planning and implementation of projects in the communities, ensuring that targets are met at most minimum cost while aiming at global best practices.

March 2017 - April 2018

Jumah Comprehensive College, Ibadan

Position: Vice Principal

• Set the school timetable, managed schedules, Facilitated parent meetings, covered various assignments as occurred.

September 2019- Till date

Amao Group of Schools

Position: Government Teacher

Prepare lesson plan, teach classes, assess student through assignments, set examinations and mark examination scripts develop easy and open rapport with students that encourage learning in a connected and enjoyable atmosphere.

Educational Qualification:

University of Ibadan, Ibadan – Msc Sociology: Industrial Sociology. **2016 -2017 University of Ibadan, Ibadan** – Bsc Sociology: **2010 -2014 Thesis:**

Bsc Sociology: Cohabitation among students of tertiary schools in Ibadan, Oyo state. 2014 Msc Sociology: Quality of education in public and private secondary schools in Ibadan. 2017

References:

1. Dr. Obemeata. .A.A Lecturer, Sociological Department University of Ibadan Tel: 08066688920

2. Mrs. Akinkuyi Bisola Head of Admin, AIICO Plot Pc12, Churchgate Street Victoria Island, Lagos

Tel: 08028407587